Guide to the Harold Thomas Fuller Husted Diaries and Diplomas
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Harold Thomas Fuller Husted diaries and diplomas
1904-1909
MS 2047
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.33
(3 boxes)
Nine diaries written by Harold Thomas Fuller Husted (1883-1956) while a Yale College student, 1904-1908, and as a graduate student, 1908-1909. Diaries are numbered 10 through 18. Also included are diplomas for his BA degree, 1908, and his master's degree, 1909. The diaries document Husted's college years in New Haven and summers at home in Westfield, NY with weekly entries. Husted consistently notes lectures; games; Yale sports, including baseball; undergraduate student life; epistolary relationships with women; the behavior of the family cat "Chimmie Fadden"; train travel; and the news.
Husted, Harold Thomas Fuller, 1883-1956
Scope and Contents
Nine diaries written by Harold Thomas Fuller Husted (1883-1956) while a Yale College student, 1904-1908, and as a graduate student, 1908-1909. Diaries are numbered 10 through 18. Also included are diplomas for his BA degree, 1908, and his master's degree, 1909.
The diaries document Husted's college years in New Haven and summers at home in Westfield, NY with weekly entries. Husted consistently notes lectures; games; Yale sports, including baseball; undergraduate student life; epistolary relationships with women; the behavior of the family cat "Chimmie Fadden"; train travel; and the news.
Arrangement
The material is arranged by type of material and therein chronologically.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Paula DeFeyter, 2016.
Biographical / Historical
Harold Thomas Fuller Husted (1883-1956, Yale College 1908 and MA 1909), graduate of Yale from Westfield, New York.
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open for research.
Husted, Harold Thomas Fuller, 1883-1956; Yale University -- Students
- Diaries
  - 1904-09-1905-08-09 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1905-08-17-1906-04-24 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1906-04-29-1906-09-30 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1906-10-03-1907-03-01 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1907-03-09-1907-07-01 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1907-07-04-1908-05-25 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1908-03-07-1908-06-18 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1908-06-19-1909-01-12 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1909-01-15-1909-08-27 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Diplomas
  - Undergraduate and graduate diplomas, 1908-1909 (Box 3, Folder 1)